# Summary\_

I'm a student, with passion for Software Engineering, digital currencies, trading and learning cutting edge technologies, currently working on multiple personal and team projects, wanting to gain experience, deliver solutions to new, challenging tasks and meet inspiring people. I'm selfmotivated and committed to personal growth, having ability to quickly develop proficiency in coding standards, tools, and best practices, offering full commitment, 12h+/day availability and ability to focus on performed tasks.

## **Projects**.

CryptoPi.js June 2018 - Present

- Developed gesture-controlled, real-time, Web Socket based cryptocurrency price-tracking app
- Utilized GDAX API, controlled hardware with Raspberry Pi/Arduino, JohnnyFive.js and Node.js
- Currently adding Google Assistant voice integration with custom commands

ShallowBlue.js May 2018 - Present

- Programmed and visualized chess AI using minimax with alfa-beta pruning
- Developed separate branches for application state based on Redux and React Context API
- · Highly focused on code readability and used modern tools such as React, ESLint, Webpack 4 and Sass
- · Currently applying deep neural network in Tensorflow.js with reinforcement learning method

**Live Sorting Test** April 2018

- · Programmed an app for testing different sorting alghoritms and comparing their big O execution time
- · Achieved high performance due to real-time, server-side, multi-threaded Node.js computing
- Designed custom API, fully mocked it with Web Workers, then built it with Express

**Interactive AVL Tree** March 2018

- Implemented an AVL Tree in Vanilla ES6+, based on Object-Oriented Programming principles
- Visualized the tree with semantic HTML5, CSS3 Grid and p5.js, then deployed app to Heroku

### **Project Offtop (Team Project)** March 2018 - Present

- · Designed and mocked big web app, that would be the dashboard of all student's activity at the university
- · Created a team of about 40 students, run a series of lectures about Front-End Development
- Delegated teams for data fetching, backend services and database creation
- Currently creating git issues, holding meetings on scalability & security and further developing API

#### **Other Notable Projects** 2017

- Developed tab sorting Chrome Extension with functional JavaScript for own convenience
- Developed Node.js app checking air pollution with geolocation and weather APIs
- Developed and fully tested MATLAB/C/C++/8051 Assembly apps being supervised by course tutors

# **Work Experience**

### Incognito Cocktail Bar/Kofeina BARTENDER, THEN PR/SOCIAL MEDIA MARKETING MANAGER

SEO SPECIALIST/UI DESIGNER/SITE ADMINISTRATOR

Wroclaw, Poland

Jul. 2016 - Present

- · Gained strong foundation on how the web and users' attention works
- Learned how to design custom UX, create products tailored to client's needs
- · Worked long hours with high performing team in fast paced, high stress environment

### Manuli Ekobal Sp. z.o.o

Wroclaw, Poland

May 2017 - May 2018

- Proposed and implemented full redesign of company's website
- · Reduced website's payload size by a third, improved page speed rankings, cut load time by 50%
- · Boosted monthly traffic from around 5k to above 13k visits/month, organized meetings, met deadlines
- Gained experience working with servers and site maintenance in big, international, B2B company

## Education

### **Wroclaw University of Science and Technology**

Wroclaw, Poland

BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING IN CONTROL ENGINEERING AND ROBOTICS

Oct. 2016 - Exp. Jun. 2021

· Took courses including Computer Science, Algorithm Design, Artificial Intelligence and Advanced Calculus & Algebra,